http://www.thesaddleryshop.co.uk/privacy-policy

Covid-19 Update: All Orders & Deliveries Will Be Fulfilled As Normal, Click For Full Details
Natural Bute Substitutes
Seasonal Supplements (flies, sweet itch, mud fever etc)
Equine Immune System Booster
Young Horse Supplements
Equine Appetisers (for fussy feeders)
Natural Bute Substitutes
Seasonal Supplements (flies, sweet itch, mud fever etc)
Equine Immune System Booster
Young Horse Supplements
Equine Appetisers (for fussy feeders)
Privacy Policy
The Saddlery Shop is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This policy (together with our terms of Website Terms & Conditions (https://www.thesaddleryshop.co.uk/terms) and any other documents referred to on it sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting www.thesaddleryshop.co.uk you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.
Information we collect from you - we will collect and process the following data about you:
Information you give us
This is information about you that you give us by filling in forms on our site www.thesaddleryshop.co.uk (our site) or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. It includes information you provide when you register to use our site, subscribe to our service, search for a product, place an order on our site, enter a competition, promotion or survey and when you report a problem with our site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information.
Information we collect about you
With regards to each of your visits to our site we will automatically collect the following information:
Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;
Information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL), clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time), products you viewed or searched for, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the page, and any phone number used to call our customer service number.
If you consent to receiving marketing communications, we will use the following information to communicate on a regular basis:
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
Your information will be passed and stored by Mailchimp for email marketing purposes only. Mailchimp will not use or share your personal information.
Uses made of the information
We use information (First Name and Email Address) held about you in the following ways:
To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;
To notify you about changes to our service;
To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
Information we collect about you. We will use this information:
To administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
To improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
As part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;
To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
To make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.
Information we receive from other sources
We will combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We will use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).
Disclosure of your information
You agree that we have the right to share your personal information with:
Any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.
Selected third parties including:
business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with you;
advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others.
analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site;
credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score where this is a condition of us entering into a contract with you.
Personal information shared includes:
First and last name
Email address
Order history including transactional data and lifetime spend
We will disclose your personal information to third parties:
In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
If The Saddlery Shop or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use (https://www.thesaddleryshop.co.uk/terms) and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of The Saddlery Shop, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Where we store your personal data
The data that we collect from you will not be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area.
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
Your rights
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at:
The Saddlery Shop
Trelawne Farm,
Chilla,
Beaworthy,
Devon,
EX21 5XE
Email: customerservices@thesaddleryshop.co.uk
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
Access to information
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act.
Please contact:
The Saddlery Shop
Trelawne Farm,
Chilla,
Beaworthy,
Devon,
EX21 5XE
Email: customerservices@thesaddleryshop.co.uk
Data deletion
You are entitled to request the deletion of all information submitted and stored by The Saddlery Shop at any time by contacting:
The Saddlery Shop
Trelawne Farm,
Chilla,
Beaworthy,
Devon,
EX21 5XE
Email: customerservices@thesaddleryshop.co.uk
Changes to our privacy policy
Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.
Contact
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to:
The Saddlery Shop
Trelawne Farm,
Chilla,
Beaworthy,
Devon,
EX21 5XE
Email: customerservices@thesaddleryshop.co.uk
STAY UP TO DATE
DEPARTMENTS
Young Rider
Lady Rider
Male Rider
Saddles & Tack
Cookies
Not the tasty chocolate chip kind, but important for you to know - we use cookies to offer you the best experience possible when shopping with us. Continue to browse if you're happy with our Privacy & Cookie Policy.
Accept & Close
